Happy Sankranti to you and all the viewers and
our team as well and if we
talk about it being true here then subscribe to our separate
appointment
and
if you
subscribe and that is why
they have but even at this time
Hanuman there is another reason due to which
you will see the target price a little bit lower
and on the basis the
execution the company has done and the addition it has made
is commendable and that is why it has decided to
increase its target price in the range of two hundred rupees from this,
especially on the remote desktop at
this point it feels that there will be buying
opportunities here and especially if you see then
their buying advice is Tata Steel and
Appointed feels that the results which are going to come will be
subscribed from here, it means that it can get better
results going forward for the
appointment of subscription and from here you should move
upwards from this appointment
if you
subscribe and
turn on then
you are Jhal Jhal Jhal